我要被你撩疯了
You drive me to madness.
让这疯癫治愈你吧
Then let madness be your medicine.
该死 我还是把缝纫包拿过来吧
Damn it. I'll get the sewing kit.
-殿下  -这位女士是我的
Your holiness! - The lady's mine.
这位女士有名字 她叫雪莉
The lady has a name. It's Shelly.
没错
- Oh, yeah.
很好
Yes.
别朝你弟弟身上吐口水啊
- Oh, don't spit on your brother!
您要的种马 我的女王
Your stallion, my queen.
我今晚要骑骑我的小马
Tonight, I'll be riding a young colt.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
来了吗
Did it work?
也许我该去问你妹
Maybe I should just ask your sister.
我俩现在在冷战 你知道的
You know I'm not talking to her right now.
或者我该问问 “威利和佛朗哥”
- Or I could ask "Willy and Franco,"
毕竟全国所有司机
since the entire drive-time audience
对我的性生活懂得比我还多
knows more about my sex life than I do.
兰伯特医生
Dr. Lambert,
人家好疼嘛
I've got the most awful ache,
只不过不是牙疼
only it's not in my tooth.
我是个牙医 兰伯特太太
I'm a dentist, Mrs. Lambert.
你可能得去看专科
Sounds like you need a specialist.
一场关于杀虫剂的致命谈话
所以 咱们今天干什么
So what's on the agenda for today?
我还没看过大都会博物馆
Oh, well, I still haven't seen
那个“挪威儿童手绘织物”展览
the "Hand-painted Textiles by Norwegian Children" exhibit
超级美妙的
at The Met. - Oh, it's a dream.
下周在时代广场的
And next week there's a production
圆形剧场
of "Mourning Becomes Electra"
还会有《悲悼》的演出
at the new Circle in the Square.
《悲悼》是由美国剧作家尤金·奥尼尔创作的剧本
该剧于1931年10月26日在百老汇的公会剧院首映
-天 我好怀念现场看剧的日子  -让我们看个够
- Oh, God, I miss live theater. - We can see it all.
不用着急回去 洛杉矶又不会跑
There's no rush. LA will always be there.
是啊 它会对我怒目而视 直至沉入海底
Yeah, glaring at me until it cracks into the sea.
布兰特 别忘了乔伊斯
Brandt, we still have Joyce.
好姑娘
Good girl.
慢慢让自己恢复 加满吗
Give yourself time to recover. Top off?
-我不介意  -好吧
- Don't mind if I do. - All right.
这是过滤过的
That is distilled.
尝尝有什么不同
Taste the difference.
谢谢
- Thank you.
你想来办公室
Do you want to swing by the office,
-跟我一起吃午饭吗  -天
meet me for lunch? - Oh, God.
不了 那场卡维特的灾难我还得
No, I have to run through the Cavett debacle
再过上几百遍 知道吗
a couple hundred more times, you know?
乔伊斯
Joyce.
麦琪 我不能去《贝琪》杂志的
Maggie, I can't show my face at "Betsy."
不要被吓到了亲爱的
Oh, honey, don't be intimidated.
就是另一本杂志而已
It's just another magazine.
我不确定诶 我只带了几套衣服
- I don't know. I only packed a couple of outfits.
-都太成熟了  -我衣橱的衣服随你挑
They're both pretty ripe. - You have my entire closet.
-咱们该走了 阳光小美女  -好的
- We gotta go, sunshine. - Okay.
我温柔地提个醒 时尚产业
A gentle reminder, the fashion industry
是世界第二大工业污染源
is the world's second-largest industrial polluter.
-求你了 救救我吧  -好吧 行吧
- Please, save me. - Okay, fine.
好 我们到时见
Okay, I'll see you there. Okay.
-我爱你  -爱你
- I love you. - You too.
好了 这就出门 这就出门
Okay. Okay, I'm going, I'm going.
-拜拜  -拜
- Bye, bye. - Bye!
-拜  -迈克帮我们在绿野酒馆
Bye. - Mike got us a reservation
订了位置 你想去吗
at Tavern on the Green, do you want to go?
给你们带来的纽约小礼物
Okay, genuine Big Apple treasure.
-有趣  -对吧 绝对的有趣
- Fun. - Right? Tons of fun.
这些虽然在洛杉矶也能买到
I mean, you can get these in LA,
但既然是你的家乡 买它做什么呢
but when it's your hometown, why bother.
有时候 只有当游客时
Sometimes, it takes being a tourist,
才会对自己好一点
you know, to treat yourself.
拿一个吧 全部拿走
Take one. Take-- take them all.
-给你们的  -乔伊斯呢
They're for you guys. - Where's Joyce?
乔伊斯需要时间
- Joyce is just taking some time
-要考虑清楚一些事  -对
to figure some things out. - Yeah.
她不会回来了吧
- She's not coming back, is she?
这是她自己的决定
It was her decision.
她有自己的想法 我尊重这一点
She's a woman with her own mind and I respect that.
不过呢 说不定她已经正在机场
That said, she's probably at the airport right now
踏上回来的路呢 但不管怎样吧
on her way back, but either way, guys,
咱们还有杂志要做呢
we got a magazine to put to bed.
乔伊斯不在还怎么做
How are we going to do that without Joyce?
奇了怪了
Oh, I don't know,
她没来之前 我们的杂志都是怎么来的
how did we do magazines before her?
我记得咱们之前发行过几百万册呢
I seem to remember publishing a few million without her.
她给了我一个活页夹 里面有所有第三期
And she gave us a binder with all of the content
所需的材料
for issue three,
我们只用拍插页就好了
so we just have to shoot the centerfold.
对
Right.
-母牛队  -是山羊队好吧
"The Cow." - "The Goat."
请大家尊重一下
Please show a little bit of respect.
两届超级碗最有价值球员好吗 里奇
He's a two-time Super Bowl MVP, Rich.
-好  -我会在拍摄现场安排保安
Okay. And I'm going to bring on some security for the shoot,
让他不用担心
so he knows he's taken care of.
他想跟裸体模特一起凹造型
And he wants to pose with a topless model.
你能找一个吗
So could you find one?
什么 他想干嘛
What? He want--
好吧 考虑到我们这期的内容
O-okay. Given what we were planning,
她得是个强壮的圣诞老妇
she'd have to be a strong Mrs. Claus
或者是一个为驯鹿权利而战的精灵
or, I don't know, an elf fighting for reindeer rights?
我们可以用亮片挡住她私密部分
We could cover her butt with tinsel.
太棒了
Great.
所以这个女人还是个装饰品喽
So this woman would be there as an ornament?
装饰品可以 但不是那种
An ornament's fun, but not one of those,
又大又圆的
like, big round ones.
对吧 要做的性感一点
Right? We want like a sexy one,
像个天使 或是性感的糖果手杖
like an angel or like a sexy candy cane, right?
道格 不符合《风骚女子》的调性
Doug, this just doesn't feel like "Minx."
好 那你也不必
Okay, then you don't have to be
当这一期的插页协调员了
the centerfold coordinator for this shoot.
你不用走啊 不参加拍摄就行了
You don't have to go now. Just skip the shoot.
没事 我有自知之明
It's fine. I know when I'm not wanted.
斑比
Bambi.
她想走 就让她走吧
- Guys, if she wants to go, let her go.
她这个职位6个月前还不存在
Her job didn't exist six months ago.
她会没事的
She'll be fine. Okay?
我们要聊聊内容设计
What we need to talk about is production design.
我有个旅行社的朋友 能帮忙搞到雪橇
I got a guy in Azusa who can get us a sleigh.
你们都有什么资源 脑暴吧
What do you got? Let's work.
麦琪马上就出来
- Maggie'll be out in a second.
谢了
Okay. Thank you.
贝琪杂志
女性联合起来
维多利亚·哈内特
要寻求解放
文秘工作的未来
-乔伊斯 -嗨
- Joyce! - Hi.
在我们离开前 我想介绍你认识伊莱恩
So before we go, I want you to meet Elayne.
天啊 现在吗
Oh, God. Now? No--
来吧 很快的
Come on. It'll be a second.
伊莱恩 我把乔伊斯·普里格带来了
- Elayne? I have Joyce Prigger.
你好 见到您
Hello. It is real--
我真想扭断那个迪克·卡维特的脖子 自命不凡的混蛋
I could just ring that smug Dick Cavett's neck
竟然那样对你
for what he put you through!
维多利亚做的也不对
And Victoria should know better too.
不过话说 她玩猜字游戏都作弊
But then again, she cheats at Scrabble,
所以我见怪不怪了
so I'm not surprised.
没事的
Oh, God, it's fine.
只是国家电视台而已咯
You know, it's just national television.
你的事我都跟伊莱恩说了
I told Elayne all about you.
是啊 你的杂志真刺激
Yes. You've had quite a ride.
天 你怎么会有这个
- Oh, my God. Where did that come from?
我收藏了你的第一期杂志 伊莱恩想看看
- I kept your debut issue. Elayne wanted to see it.
啊 麦琪 我这是班门弄斧了
- Oh, my God, Maggie. That is so amateurish.
虽然还有改进的地方 但内容很强大
I-- I found it raw, but powerful.
谢谢您 这话对我太重要了
Thank you. That means-- that means a lot.
《风骚女子》还有很长的路要走
You know, "Minx" is a long way from this.
艺术总要抱住商业的邪恶大腿的
- Well, the unholy marriage of art and commerce.
这一点你肯定懂
I'm sure you can relate.
我们《贝琪》杂志
Mm, we're in a bit of a privileged position
在一点上有特权
here at "Betsy." - Mm-hmm.
一份威望闪闪的新出版物
Shiny new prestige publication--
费尔柴尔德出版社的亏本买卖
a loss leader for Fairchild.
他们不指望我们盈利
They don't expect us to make a profit.
他们只想赔本赚吆喝
They just love the good write-ups.
那广告呢
What about advertising?
我们偶尔会向一个
- Oh, we do book the occasional ad
使命驱动的非营利组织接广告
for a mission-driven nonprofit,
但那点钱都不够付房租的
but we don't need it to pay the rent.
乔伊斯 我们很乐意邀请你一道
Joyce, we would love to invite you in.
为我们写篇文章吧 你的故事太迷人了
Write a piece for us. You have a fascinating story.
真是个好生意
That is such a good idea.
她是不是很棒
She's amazing, isn't she?
好了 我带你参观下哈
Okay, do you want a quick tour?
-好  -你看
- Yes. - All right.
这里是我们的编辑部
So our editorial department lives in here.
我们部门在外面 排版 你好
Our department's out there, layouts, hi.
还有 这是我最喜欢 这个可爱的研讨角
Oh, my favorite-- my favorite is this little research nook.
天啊 这里的温度特别宜人
God, the temperature, it's so cozy.
永远都设在华氏74度
Always set to 74.
如果你觉得冷 有小毯子
And if you get a chill, shahtooshes,
是由藏羚羊的羊毛制成
made from the wool of Tibetan chiru antelopes.
我邀请了其他几个同事跟我们一起吃午饭
So I invited some of the ladies to join us for lunch,
不过你如果只想跟我吃的话
but if you want it to just be us--
-没事 多多益善  -太好了 走吧
- No, the more the merrier. - All right, shall we?
走吧 这边走
Let's-- okay, this way.
-我们说到哪儿了  -条款
- Where were we? - Terms.
连完整的编辑团队都没有
Well, I couldn't possibly consider
我是不会认真考虑的
without a full editorial staff.
有道理
Sounds fair to me.
出差头等舱
First-class travel.
国内航班
Domestic.
外加国际航班
And international.
我不去米兰参加几个时装周
If I'm not in Milan for Fashion Week,
《风骚女子》还怎么跻身时尚圈
"Minx" will never be relevant in the style space.
顺便一提 霍尔斯顿会喜欢你的
And Halston would love you, by the way.
大家都爱我
Oh, everybody loves me.
我喜欢你的直白 但我还在考虑很多候选人
I like your spunk but you're not my only date to the dance.
你的名片夹里难不成还有海伦·格里·布朗么
Yes, I'm sure you have Helen Gurley Brown in your Rolodex.
说实话 确实有
Oh, I do.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
听我说 你知道《风骚女子》有多火
Listen, you know how hot "Minx" is
否则你也不会来见我
or you wouldn't have taken this meeting.
我马上就要成为全国最炙手可热的成人杂志
I'm about to have the number one adult mag in the country
而你想来分一杯羹
and we both know you want to be a part of that.
所以我会考虑你提出的条件 但目前来看
So I'll consider your terms, but as of now,
米兰只能你自己出钱了
Milano's on your dime.
巧克力塔 酸橙派
Chocolate tart? Key lime pie?
买单
Just the check.
还有21年的单一麦芽威士忌
And that 21-year single malt.
马上来
Coming up.
我不知道还能去哪
I didn't know where else to go.
我在底袋钱没什么可做的
There's nothing left for me to do at Bottom Dollar.
抱歉斑比 我不知道乔伊斯去哪了
I'm so sorry, Bambi. I don't know where Joyce is.
我其实已经把她给拉黑了
She's on my shit list, in fact.
我知道你很生气 但你和莱尼之间发生的
- I get that you're mad, but isn't it kind of good,
都是好事啊
what happened with you and Lenny?
现在他知道自己没法带你登上月球了
I mean, now that he knows he can't take you to the moon,
但至少也有地方可去啊
at least you can get somewhere.
去哪 离婚厅吗
What? Like divorce court?
我试过道歉
I tried to apologize,
但我们好像也没有复合的可能了
but we can't seem to get back on track.
你只需要重新找回最佳状态就行
You just need to re-notch your groove.
你能接受在沙漠中裸体吗
How do you feel about getting naked in the desert?
-不行  -好吧 看来吃麦斯卡灵是不行了
- No. - Okay, so mescaline's out.
喝点优尼特已经够了
Yeah. Riunite's as crazy as we get.
你可以来点更嗨的
You can get crazier than that.
性感的如何
What about something sexy?
-我弄不来性感的  -谢莉
- I don't do sexy. - Shelly.
你有一头明星范儿的头发
You have the hair of a starlet
还有希腊女神般的翘臀
and the hips of a Greek goddess.
我见过那些雕塑行吗
I've seen those statues. Okay?
我觉得有点像面团
They're kind of doughy.
那种身材男人最爱
Dough gets pounded.
-你给她开价多少  -别操心钱的事了
- You offered her how much? - Don't worry about that.
再说了 如果她能完成承诺的一半
Plus she's gonna be worth ten times that if she delivers
那我们就能赚回十倍的钱
on half the stuff she promised.
她那人脉
I mean, with her connections--
你到底给她多少钱
But what salary did you offer her?
我们谈的是电影 时尚
- We're talking about film. We're talking about fashion.
美容
We're talking about beauty.
我们甚至可以赞助爵士音乐节
I mean, we could sponsor a jazz festival.
跟赫比·汉考克拉上关系
Hobnobbin' with Herbie Hancock.
别跟我说你不想要
Don't tell me you wouldn't want that, Tins.
别拿赫比诱惑我
Don't tease me with Herbie.
再见了 新大厦
Bye-bye, new building.
不不不 你应该说 你好啊 新帝国
Oh, no, no. Hello, new empire.
我是说 人生中能有几次机会
I mean, how many opportunities in life
走在世上的尖端呢
do you get to catch the big wave?
这可是个绝佳的机会
This is the big one.
好吧 乔伊斯走了才5天吧
- Okay, Joyce has been gone, what, five days?
我们能放慢点脚步吗 这些决定可都不是小事
Can we slow down? These are huge decisions.
不行
No way, not a chance.
我们现在可不能放慢脚步
This is the time to make a big move.
好嘞 雷内蒂牌意面
Voila. Spaghetti Renetti.
-这明明是阿尔弗雷多意面  -什么
- This is Spaghetti Alfredo. - Excuse me?
阿尔弗雷多让你这么说的吗
Did Alfredo tell you to say that?
他好像是提过一嘴
He might've mentioned something.
这绝对是我的意面 阿尔弗雷多这么说可过了
That is my spaghetti. Alfredo is out of line.
嘿 你说 你说出来
Hey, you say it. You say it.
阿尔弗雷多 你靠边站
Alfredo, you're out of line.
谢谢 我就想听你这么说
Thank you. I needed to hear it.
蒂娜 我想让你做
Hey, I want you to be the managing editor
《风骚女子》的总编
of "Minx", Tins.
温迪是个大牌 她视角新奇
Look, Wendy's a big name. She's got big ideas.
但每天日常开销管理
But day-to-day production spending,
我只信得过你来负责
you're the only person I trust and you know it.
你想让我担任这个职位
You're giving me this job now.
是的
Yes, I am.
亚历克斯是一名餐厅评论家
So Alex is a restaurant critic.
真不敢相信我们要请他吃饭
I can't believe we're serving him dinner.
我还不如自杀算了
Why don't I just kill myself?
乔治娜 你以前在贝琪见过她
Georgina, you met earlier at "Betsy."
她是个助理编辑 她爸是联合利华的负责人
She's an assistant editor and her dad runs Unilever.
埃里克为林德赛市长工作
And Eric works for Mayor Lindsay.
林德赛的业绩都有他的一份子
He's responsible for everything good Lindsay's ever done.
还有 他单身哦
And, uh, he's single.
-是嘛  -嗯嗯
- Oh, really. - Mm-hmm.
不过提醒你一下哈 他喜欢把“生意”说“身意”
Only thing to know is that he says, um, "busimess."
你别在意哈
It's not a big deal.
你是说他提到生意这个词时
Are you saying he says "busimess"
会说成身意
instead of "business?" - Mm-hmm.
没人告诉他吗
Well, has anybody told him?
-没有  -那今晚就有了
- No. - Tonight's the night.
不行 乔伊斯 你别告诉他
No, Joyce, you can't tell him.
-我必须说  -不 你
- I'm gonna tell him. - No, you--
你为什么不能搬回纽约来呢
Why can't you move back to New York?
我好想你
I miss you.
天 别勾引我
- Oh, God. Don't tempt me.
这些农民太短见了
These farmers are so short-sighted.
他们连5分钟之外的前景都看不到
They can't see five minutes into the future.
-可不是  -我同意
Right. - I agree.
如果战后政府没有
- Maybe if the government hadn't shoved it
逼他们这么做的话
down their throats after the war,
我们一开始就不会有这种问题
we wouldn't have this problem to begin with.
不不不 如果杀虫剂能够挽救家庭农场
- No, no, no, if DDT is going to save the family farm,
那我们有什么权力指手画脚
then who are we to judge?
那些会因为癌症而死的人
· The people who are going to die of cancer.
看着生态系统
Yeah, and watch as the ecosystems fail
因所有鸟类都会灭绝了
because all the birds have gone extinct.
只要鸡肉不灭绝就行
As long as we still have Cornish hens.
好吧 除了这些
- Right, except for those. Yes.
晚餐真不错 亲爱的
They're delicious, love.
西塔蕾拉从不让人失望
Oh, well, Citarella never disappoints.
天 好想念这一切
- Oh, my God. I've missed this.
我都不记得最后一次
I cannot remember the last time
谈论杀虫剂这么有趣的话题
I had a scintillating conversation
是什么时候了
about a lethal pesticide.
悲剧了 冰块没了
- Oh, no, tragedy. That's the last of the ice.
-布兰特  -就喝红酒呗
- Brandt-- - Just stick to the wine.
挺好喝的
It's delicious.
你喜欢的 多好喝
You love it. It's great.
你手里有放了冰块的威士忌当然这么说
Says the man with ice in his whiskey.
真是太丢脸了 十分抱歉
I'm humiliated. I am so sorry.
可不是
You should be.
好吧
Okay.
好了
All right. Okay.
他在里面怎么样
How's he doing in there?
-不清楚  -是吗
- Unclear. - Yeah?
很多噪音
There are a lot of noises.
-噪音哈  -很吵
- Lot of noises, huh? - A lot.
噪音好啊
Noises are okay.
你怎么样
How you doing?
姑娘们已经准备好了 我们都准备好了
Girls are ready. We're ready.
你快完事了吗
You close?
完事这词是用在娘娘腔身上的
Close is for pussies.
要么能“干” 要么滚蛋
You're either there or you're nowhere.
好了
All right.
搞起来
Let's do this.
开工
Get to work. Let's go!
来了 姑娘们 比利·布兰森
We got him, ladies, Billy Brunson.
美国的钢琴家、乐队指挥和作曲家
他那活可真硬啊
That is a very hard dick.
-是吗  -我们这没法拍啊
Oh, you think? - We can't shoot that.
除非你不在乎自己的杂志都没人敢摆在展架上
Unless you want a magazine no one can put on their stands.
我不知道 能不能让拍摄角度
I don't know, I was thinking maybe
好一点 可以稍微
you could do some kind of camera trick or an angle
避开点他那里
that kind of hides it a little bit.
那我就只能调曝光度了
Sure, I'll just set the exposure to flaccid.
雷内蒂 拍不拍啊
Renetti, this happenin' or what, buddy?
拍 拍
Yes. Yes.
我能跟你说句话吗
Can I get a moment with you, please?
-行  -好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我喜欢你的选择 十分大胆
I love this choice. I think it's bold.
但我想说的是 也许给我们的读者
But I got to say, I find with our readers,
一些想象空间更好
it's-- it's better to sometimes give them a bite
就不用那么直接 你明白我的意思吧
rather than the whole meal, don't you?
你这话说给其他男模特听还能糊弄的过去
You might get away with that bullshit with your male models.
我这可不行
But not with me.
既然你想要历史最佳 那你就得让大家见识一下什么叫最佳
You asked for The Goat, you're gettin' all of The Goat.
我不 我不知道黑色行不行
I don't-- I don't know about black.
汤米这么多年一直穿黑的
It was the only color Tommy wore for years.
主要是黑色和什么都很搭
On the plus side, black goes with everything.
帮他搭配衣服简直太容易了
So getting him dressed was a breeze.
但是
But, you know--
谢丽 在这个家里 你不需要做个母亲
Shelly, in this home, you don't have to be a mom.
而且你看上去很美
And you look great.
我都认不出来自己了
I don't recognize myself.
就是要这样啊
That's the point.
好吧
Okay.
谢丽
Shelly...
让我们见识一下谢丽吧
- Meet Shelly. That's you, too.
她把自己隐藏了太久
She's just been hiding for a while.
想要跟你老公重拾旧好
In order to find magic with your husband,
你得先发现自身的美好
you have to find it first in yourself.
-乔伊斯  -嗯
- So, Joyce-- - Yes.
你要在纽约待多久
- How long will you be in New York?
通常我会计划好一切
Well, usually I have everything planned.
一切 但这次我说不好
Everything. But I don't know.
她会在《贝琪》上写一篇关于我们的文章
- She's writing a piece for us at "Betsy" actually.
那可不错啊 哪方面的
- Good for you. What about?
我 不 我还没答应呢
I-- no-- I have not said yes yet.
厉害 可以多要点钱
Smart. Hold out for more money.
我可以帮你
- I can help you with that.
谢谢 谢谢你
- Well, thank you. Thank you.
-好  -你有人脉
Okay, good. - You got people.
不是这么回事 伊莱恩想让我写写《风骚女子》的事
It's-- no, Elayne wants me to write about "Minx".
哎呀
Yikes.
麦琪让我们什么都别说
- Maggie told us not to say anything.
没有 没有
No. No.
我说的是 别逼她
What I said is, "Don't push her."
没事 没事
No, it's fine. It's fine.
我不介意朋友之间谈论这个
I don't mind talking about it amongst friends.
-真好  -天
- Great. - Oh, God.
我确实有个问题
I do have one question.
-当然  -他开始了
- Of course. - There he is.
那个男人
The men. - Mm-hmm?
-是个牛郎对吧  -不 不是
- Gigolos, right? - No, no.
第一张插页是一名消防员
The first centerfold was a firefighter.
第二张是茱莉亚音乐学院的毕业生
And the second was a Juilliard grad.
真的吗
- Really? - Mm-hmm.
看看
Look at that.
他的父母一定高兴的要起舞了
His parents must be dancing.
谁在乎男人啊
Who cares about the men?
我们只是想更了解女人
We want to know about the women.
谁会做这种事情
Who ends up doing something like that?
很显然 那些不得不这么做的人
Obviously, somebody who has to.
欲望强的
- Mm. - A runaway.
或者单身母亲
Or a single mother.
不 我的设想不是这样的
No. That's not been my experience.
你听到了吗 乔治娜
You hear that, Georgina?
未经他人苦
Don't judge until you've street-walked
莫劝他人善
a mile in their stilettos.
这些女人其实和我们并没有太大的不同
These women aren't actually that different from us.
她们只是
You know, they just are
想让自己的身体更舒服些
more comfortable with their bodies.
乔伊斯 他们和我们不一样
Joyce. They're nothing like us.
记住 你是一个耀眼
Now remember, you are a dazzling,
闪亮 性感的女神
glimmering, sexy nymph.
女神喜欢藏在东西后面
- Oh, nymphs like to hide behind things.
也许我该躲在沙发后面或者
Maybe I'll just pop behind the couch or--
不不不
No, no, no.
来吧 你超性感
Come on, you're hot.
行 我热的冒汗 我穿着毛线衫呢
Yeah, I'm sweating. I'm a sweater.
好了 带上这个
Okay. Take this.
真漂亮啊
Oh. This is nice.
我的幸运手镯
My good luck charm.
我第一次拍照时就带着它
I wore it on my very first photoshoot.
一千零一夜
"101 Arabian Nights."
是那个一千零一夜吗
Oh, isn't it "One Thousand and One Arabian Nights"?
是的 我们的预算很低
Yeah. Ours was pretty low budge.
我也像你现在一样紧张
But I was nervous like you are now
但我挺过来了 之后也没发生什么坏事
and I got through it and nothing bad's happened since.
这简直是连胜啊
- Wow, that's quite a hot streak.
对 连胜
Yes. Hot.
说到这个
Speaking of hot,
你身上充满了神秘 十分热辣
you are on fire and you have a secret.
什么意思
Ooh. What is it?
不知道
I don't know.
这是你和摄影机之间的事情
It's between you and the camera.
你很会啊
Oh, you're good.
嘿 比利
Hey, Billy.
能和我单独聊聊吗
Can I have one more can I have a moment?
这太棒了 太令人激动了
Yeah. This is great. This is exciting.
我能和你说实话吗
Can I be totally honest with you?
这不是我说了算的
It's-- it's not up to me.
我是说我可以拍这些照片
I mean, I can take these photos,
但传播这些照片是违法的
but it's not legal for me to distribute them.
我的老二可是凌驾于法律之上的 兄弟
My dick is above the law, brother.
嗯 我也希望是这样 相信我
Yeah, I wish that was true. Believe me.
但如果我们把裸露度降到75%呢
But what if we took it down to 75%?
75%怎么样 比利
Can we do 75%, Billy?
-只露出四分之三  -对
- Three-quarter mast. - Yeah.
你要是看到美国国旗降下三分之一
Is that how you like to salute your flag?
是什么感受
In America?
嘿 我和你一样是个爱国者
Hey, I'm a patriot just like you.
但如果你想让你的美国朋友看到这东西
But if you want your fellow Americans to see this thing,
当然我们都他妈想看
which we both fucking do,
但我们得稍微降低点
we gotta let a little air out of the tire down here.
我们得这么做
We just gotta.
-90%  -这个
- 90%. - That's--
80%吧 我们降到80%
Give me 80. Let's go down to 80.
-没门  -可以的
- No way. - Yes.
没门 兄弟 这可是上等好货
No way, brother. This is grade A beef.
拜托
Come on.
不 后退 伙计 不不
Oh no, step back, son. No, no.
大家都得裸着
Everybody stays naked.
我知道你很想要我
I know you want me hard.
所以你为什么不把这个坏小子拍进去呢
So why don't you just take this bad boy in?
你可以看但不能摸
You can look but don't touch.
我们来开拍吧 行吗
Let's start shooting. Right?
我们来寻找一种双方都满意的办法
Let's find a level that works for everybody.
但现在我们先来拍摄 好吗
But the move now is to start shooting, right?
对对 让这些女孩跳起来吧
Yeah, yeah, let's get these girlies jumping up and down.
-让这些铃铛响起来  -我喜欢这种活力
I want these jingles jangling. - Ooh, I love that energy!
女孩们 来跳起来
Girls, let's jump.
像他说的那样让铃铛响起来
Let's get the jingles jangling like he said.
这和教育有关
It's about education.
想想看 如果有人足够关心 让他们继续接受教育
Just think of how much better these people's lives could be
这些人的生活该有多好
if somebody just cared enough to keep them in school.
我不认为受过教育的人
You know, I don't think that educated people
可以垄断决策权
have a monopoly on good decision-making.
瓦萨学院的学生毕业后沦落到色情行业
An excellent point from the Vassar grad
然后在这儿提出了一个多棒的论点啊
who ended up in porno.
她不会一直干那个的
She didn't "end up" there.
她只是暂时驻足
She was slumming it for a while,
沾染点凡间的尘埃
getting a little dirt under the nails.
好吧 但故事有个圆满的结局
Well, the story has a happy ending
因为乔伊斯回到了属于她的纽约
because Joyce is back in New York where she belongs.
-敬乔伊斯  -敬乔伊斯
To Joyce. all: To Joyce.
敬乔伊斯
To Joyce.
上周我遇到了威廉·肖恩
So I ran into William Shawn last week,
-顺便说一句 他看起来很糟糕  -当然了
who looks awful, by the way. - Well, of course.
我去拿些冰来
I'll get more ice.
不 你不必这么做的
No, you don't have to do that.
不不不 没关系
No, no, no. It's fine.
我还没感受纽约秋天的空气
I never get to breathe fall air.
好吧 我有没有告诉过你
- All right. Did I tell you...
道格 看看周围
Doug, look around.
这真的符合《风骚女子》的主题吗
Is this really what "Minx" is about?
现在就别在这儿唧唧歪歪的了
Don't do that whiny shit right now.
-你听到了吗  -没有 我知道他是个大人物
You hear me? - No, I know he's a big get.
但是 道格 我们在这儿干嘛呢
But, Doug, what are we doing here?
我不能一整天都让这玩意立着
I can't keep this thing up all day long.
不然他们以为我们在干什么
What do they think we're doing?
我们时间有限 莱博维茨
We're on limited time here, Leibovitz.
-开始拍吧  -再给我们几分钟时间 好吗
Start shooting. - Just give me a second, okay?
拜托就按快门吧 我们拍点什么出来
Just please press the button. Let's shoot something.
我不能一整天都站着
I can't stand here all day.
拍照吧 里奇
Take the pics, Richie.
选好角度 拍照吧
Read the room and take the pics.
-好吧  -真好
- Fine. - Good.
别傻了 快按快门
Don't be an asshole, press the button.
我在按
I am.
要是觉得这太为难你了
Why don't you go rouge some nipples
不如去给乳头补补妆 里奇
if this is so beneath you, Rich?
-行吗 我来拍 里奇 谢谢  -我知道了
Okay? I got it. Thanks, Richie. Thank you.
很好
Oh, great.
那现在这屋子里就有两个硬了的男的了
Now there's two hard dicks in the room.
很好 我们很好
- Oh, ho! Pretty good. We're good.
这就是你控制局面的方式啊 雷内蒂
That's how you take control, Renetti.
伙计
My man.
和你的男朋友玩得开心
Have fun with your boyfriend.
粗燕麦粉和煎饼 你们觉得怎么样 伙计们
Grits and pancakes. What do you say, guys?
很好 兴奋起来 激动起来
Good. Excitement, excitement.
比利·布伦森来了
We got Billy Brunson.
很好
Great.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事 你真美
Nothing. You're gorgeous.
我只是想稍微调整一下你的头发
I just want to adjust your hair a little bit.
好吧 随你
Yeah, do whatever you want.
然后调整下袍子
Um, and then the robe,
我在想肩膀这里可以
I was thinking maybe it could be a little
松开一点
off the shoulders or--
不要袍子怎么样
What about no robe?
就这么拍
That's the shot.
杂货和熟食店
我能请你喝一杯吗
Can I buy you a drink?
如果我同意 你能别再跟着我了吗
If I say yes, will you stop following me?
我知道那道鸡肉有点干 但
I know the Cornish hen was a bit dry, but...
抱歉
Um, I'm sorry.
好吧 我去跳舞了
Okay, I just-- I went dancing.
半路离开晚宴吗
In the middle of a dinner party?
那是吻痕吗
Is that a hickey?
是
Yeah.
我遇到一个人
I met somebody.
他是谁
So who was he?
你连他的名字都不知道
You don't even know his name.
我只知道他不是那种
You know what I know is that he wasn't
居高临下看别人的人
patronizing and judgmental.
成熟点吧 乔伊斯
Oh, grow up, Joyce.
你以为格洛丽亚·斯泰纳姆去参加晚宴
You think when Gloria Steinem goes to a dinner party,
人们不会问她在花花公子俱乐部
people don't ask her about her time
做卧底的事吗
going undercover at The Playboy Club?
这就是你现在有趣的地方
It's what makes you interesting right now.
我的生活不是你晚宴的素材
- My life is not fodder for your dinner party.
但在适合的场合接受关注
But you're more than happy
更开心不是吗
to Iap up the attention when it suits you.
你的开心建立在我的窘态上
You're more than happy basking in my reflection.
这个
This--
我只是想让你重新回归正常生活
I'm trying to give you back your life.
好吧 好吧
Okay. All right.
这是可以挽回的 好吧
This is salvageable. All right?
我
I, uh--
我有些信纸
I have some stationery.
你可以写些道歉信
You can write some apology notes
施展普里格魅力
and break out that Prigger charm.
我没什么可道歉的
- I have nothing to apologize for.
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
这真是你想要的吗
Is this what you wanted?
会让杂志大卖的 对吧
- It'll move magazines, all right?
我会开始寻找新的摄影师
I'll start looking for new photographers.
你可能要把乔伊斯的名字从杂志上删掉了
You should probably take Joyce's name off the masthead.